

Personal

Indio, California

Location

(909)-205-6607 Phone

hola@godiego.me

https://www.godiego.me/

Languages

English ★★★★

Spanish ★★★★

French ★★☆☆☆

Skills

HTML5 ★★★★

Git ★★★☆

Javascript ★★★☆

NodeJS ★★☆☆

jQuery ★★★★

AngularJS ★★★★
Bootstrap 3/4 ★★★★

Firebase ★★★☆☆

SQL ★★★☆☆

C# ★★★☆☆

ASP.NET MVC ★★★☆☆

Full list of skills can be found on my website

Diego Bernal

Web Developer

Software developer with an engineering background, specializing in web technologies. Possesses strong problem-solving skills and an affinity for clean, maintainable, readable and reusable code and best practices. Experienced in developing static websites and complex, multi-layer web applications.

Experience

Readylink Healthcare

olonor

Web Developer

- Designed and developed ASP .NET MVC application with Bootstrap 3, jQuery, SQL and C#
- Designed and developed Single Page Application with AngularJS
- Developed build scripts to bundle and minify SPA for production with Gulp
- Provided test coverage for software through unit, end-to-end, and integration testing.

Freelance Developer

2016 - Present

June 2014 - Present

A list of my work can be found on my website at https://www.godiego.me/portfolio

· Build, manage, deploy web projects specified by clients

CSU San Bernardino

June 2010 - June 2014

Student Assistant

- Lead, train student staff about proper protocol in dealing with resident students
- Place and take phone calls
- Verify and file maintenance work orders
- Maintain and reconcile student housing key logs
- Provide basic maintenance and housekeeping to student residential spaces

Education

| Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering CSU San Bernardino | Sept 2009 - June 2014 |
|--|-----------------------|
| Minor in Applied Physics CSU San Bernardino | Sept 2009 - June 2014 |
| Minor in Mathematics CSU San Bernardino | Sept 2009 - June 2014 |